# Ceri May Dorsey-Tyler

[LinkedIn] | [Github]

#### **SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

I am a highly motivated and enthusiastic software engineer with a passion for problem-solving and creating efficient solutions. My journey in technology started while working as a bartender where I developed a strong customer-focused mindset and a keen eye for detail for over a decade. I am now eager to bring my customer-focused approach, drive for excellence, and technical abilities to a company where I can continue to grow and make an impact.

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Programming Languages: Javascript, CSS, HTML, Ruby on Rails
- Frameworks and Technologies: React, Redux, Tailwind
- Operating Systems: Windows, macOS
- Currently Exploring: Typescript, Python, MongoDB

## **TECHNICAL PROJECTS**

# Yes Chef - Github

""Yes Chef!" is a restaurant inventory app developed using React and Ruby on Rails."

- With its intuitive interface, the app makes it easy to add, update, and remove items from the inventory.
- Issued the functionality for users to see when their stock was running low, and resupply when needed.

## Wander - Github

"Wander is a niche travel blog that showcases unique experiences."

- Set up authorization and authentication for users to log in, log out and sign up
- Paired-programming project developed with React.js and Ruby on Rails

## GoT or NoT - Github

"A Game of Thrones meets Grand Theft Auto with a dash of satire dating site."

- Established a unique page through fun ideas and creative CSS
- Provided users the ability to playfully add characters, and delete characters by "swiping right"

## **EXPERIENCE**

**Scope Realty** Brooklyn, NY 09/2020 - 07/2021

Licensed Real Estate Agent

- Liaised with clients through active listening, clear and concise verbal and written communication, and the ability to negotiate effectively.
- Understood the financial aspects of real estate transactions, including mortgages, loans, and closing costs, as well as able to explain these concepts to clients in a clear and understandable way.
- Comfortable with technology, including using customer relationship management (CRM) software, online marketing tools, and virtual communication platforms.

Le Fanfare Brooklyn, NY 06/2019 - 08/2020 Bartender

- Responsible for a strong knowledge of spirits, beers and wine
- Maintained a professional and friendly demeanor at all times
- Created strong relationships with guests through personalized experiences

**Lobster Joint** Brooklyn, NY 02/2016 - 08/2019 Manager

- Maintained inventory and record-keeping for food and beverage sales
- Kept a strong work ethic in a fast paced environment

## **EDUCATION**

**Flatiron School** NY, NY